https://batyotto.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy PolicyOUR COMMITMENT TO YOUR PRIVACY Privacy is a viable concern for Internet users, as well as for companies doing business on the Web. Because we are committed to the privacy rights of our users, we fully disclose our privacy policies so visitors can understand what kind of information we capture and how we subsequently use that information. All personally identifiable information is managed with the utmost confidentiality.Personally identifiable information collected We collect information about our users in two ways: implicitly and explicitly. We learn about our visitors implicitly through the use of Web Analytics, which is a website activity analysis solution. Additionally, we collect personal data in order to fulfill users’ requests for additional information about our legal services. Web Analytics collects visitor information like user domain, browser, and most popular pages. This information is based on each visit, not each user, and is stored in a database. The information we gather through our use of Web Analytics is for the sole purpose of refining the content on our site. The forms on our site give visitors the opportunity to request services or request more information about our product offerings.Links to other sites Our site may contain links to other sites. Please remember that the privacy practices of these sites may differ from ours. If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your interactions with this site, you can contact us using our online form.
